(Jesse:)Haven't seen you in forever.
Look how gray you've gotten.
(Stuart:)My hair's exactly
the same color as always.
(Jesse:)No, I was talking about your skin.
Look... my friend here
needs a comic book--
Ooh! And she went into
your store by mistake.
(Jesse:)Good thing there was no
one there to see you.
(Jesse:)What do you need?
(Jesse:)Oh, yeah, yeah. I got this.
Right over here.
(Stuart:)Even you, Sweatpants?
(Sweatpants:)Free popcorn.
(Jesse:)Can I offer you a coffee?
(Jesse:)-Espresso? Latte?
-No, thanks.
(Jesse:)How about you, Stu?
Mocha? Scone?
(Jesse:)Directions to the
nearest soup kitchen?
(Sheldon:)-Hey.
-I'm just kidding.
(Jesse:)He knows where the soup kitchen is.
(Stuart:)It's on Merton Avenue.
(Bernadette:)I don't think I like the way
you're treating my friend.
(Sheldon:)Sorry.
-You want the book or nut?
-Not from you.
(Bernadette:)Let's go, Stuart.